Guide to George Mason University Faculty Course Evaluations
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
- GMU Archives- Faculty/Course Evaluations
  - Art Studio- Spring 1991 (Box Box 76)
  - Astronomy- Spring 1991 (Box Box 76)
  - Biology and Lab (Box Box 76)
  - Business Legal Studies- Spring 1991 (Box Box 76)
  - Chemistry- Spring 1991 (Box Box 76)
  - Classics- Spring 1991 (Box Box 76)
  - Communications- Spring 1991 (Box Box 76)
  - Computer Science- Spring 1991 (Box Box 76)
  - Conflict Management- Spring 1991 (Box Box 76)
  - Contract Courses- Spring 1991 (Box Box 76)
  - English- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - European Studies- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - Finance- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - Foreign Languages- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - French- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - GECA- Geographic and Cartographic Sciences- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - Geography- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - Geology- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - German- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - Government- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - Health, Sports and Leisure- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - History- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - INFS- Information Systems (Box Box 75)
  - INFT- Information Technology- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - INTL- International Transactions- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - IRM- Information Resource Management- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - Italian- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - Japanese- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - Latin- Spring 1991 (Box Box 75)
  - Law- Spring 1991 (Box Box 74)
  - Management- Spring 1991 (Box Box 74)
  - Marketing- Spring 1991 (Box Box 74)
  - Math- Spring 1991 (Box Box 74)
  - Music- Spring 1991 (Box Box 74)
  - Nursing- Spring 1991 (Box Box 74)
  - Operations Research- Spring 1991 (Box Box 74)
  - PAGE Program- Spring 1991 (Box Box 74)
  - Philosophy and Religion- Spring 1991 (Box Box 74)
  - CORE- Spring 1991 (Box Box 73)
  - Dance- Spring 1991 (Box Box 73)
  - Decision Sciences- Spring 1991 (Box Box 73)
  - Economics- Spring 1991 (Box Box 73)
  - Education- Spring 1991 (Box Box 73)
  - Engineering- Spring 1991 (Box Box 73)
  - ECE- Electrical and Computer Engineering- Spring 1991 (Box Box 73)
  - English- Spring 1991 (Box Box 73)
  - Public Affairs- Fall 1990 (Box Box 72)
  - Sociology- Fall 1990 (Box Box 72)
  - University Courses- Fall 1990 (Box Box 72)
  - Mathematical Sciences- Fall 1990 (Box Box 71)
  - Music- Fall 1990 (Box Box 71)
  - Nursing- Fall 1990 (Box Box 71)
  - OP RSCH and APPL STAT- Fall 1990 (Box Box 71)
  - PAGE Program- Fall 1990 (Box Box 71)
  - Philosophy and Religion- Fall 1990 (Box Box 71)
  - Physics- Fall 1990 (Box Box 71)
  - Psychology- Fall 1990 (Box Box 71)
  - Health, Sport and Leisure- Fall 1990 (Box Box 70)
  - History- Fall 1990 (Box Box 70)
  - Info. Sci. and Sys. Engr.- Fall 1990 (Box Box 70)
  - International Trans.- Fall 1990 (Box Box 70)
  - Law School- Fall 1990 (Box Box 70)
  - Management- Fall 1990 (Box Box 70)
  - Marketing- Fall 1990 (Box Box 70)
  - English- Fall 1990 (Box Box 69)
  - Finance- Fall 1990 (Box Box 69)
  - Foreign Languages- Fall 1990 (Box Box 69)
  - Geology- Fall 1990 (Box Box 69)
  - Conflict Resolution- Fall 1990 (Box Box 68)
  - Contract Courses- Fall 1990 (Box Box 68)
  - Core Curriculum- Fall 1990 (Box Box 68)
  - Dance and Theatre (Box Box 68)
  - Decision Sciences- Fall 1990 (Box Box 68)
  - Economics- Fall 1990 (Box Box 68)
  - Education- Fall 1990 (Box Box 68)
  - Educ Lead and Human Dev- Fall 1990 (Box Box 68)
  - Elect. and Computer Engr.- Fall 1990 (Box Box 68)
  - Accounting- Fall 1990 (Box Box 67)
  - American Studies- Fall 1990 (Box Box 67)
  - Art History- Fall 1990 (Box Box 67)
  - Art Studio- Fall 1990 (Box Box 67)
  - Biology- Fall 1990 (Box Box 67)
  - Biology Lab- Fall 1990 (Box Box 67)
  - Chemistry- Fall 1990 (Box Box 67)
  - Communications- Fall 1990 (Box Box 67)
  - Computer Science- Fall 1990 (Box Box 67)
  - Physics- Spring 1990 (Box Box 66)
  - Psychology- Spring 1990 (Box Box 66)
  - Public Affairs- Spring 1990 (Box Box 66)
  - ROTC- Spring 1990 (Box Box 66)
  - Social Work- Spring 1990 (Box Box 66)
  - Sociology- Spring 1990 (Box Box 66)
  - University Courses- Spring 1990 (Box Box 66)
  - Law School- Spring 1990 (Box Box 65)
  - Management- Spring 1990 (Box Box 65)
  - Marketing- Spring 1990 (Box Box 65)
  - Mathematical Sciences- Spring 1990 (Box Box 65)
  - Music- Spring 1990 (Box Box 65)
  - Nursing- Spring 1990 (Box Box 65)
  - Operations Research and Applied Statistics- Spring 1990 (Box Box 65)
  - PAGE- Spring 1990 (Box Box 65)
  - Philosophy and Religion- Spring 1990 (Box Box 65)
  - English- Spring 1990 (Box Box 64)
  - Finance- Spring 1990 (Box Box 64)
  - Foreign Languages- Spring 1990 (Box Box 64)
  - Geology- Spring 1990 (Box Box 64)
  - Health, Sports and Leisure- Spring 1990 (Box Box 64)
  - History- Spring 1990 (Box Box 64)
  - Information Science and Systems Engineering- Spring 1990 (Box Box 64)
  - Decision Sciences- Spring 1990 (Box Box 63)
  - Dance and Theatre- Spring 1990 (Box Box 63)
  - Economics- Spring 1990 (Box Box 63)
  - Electrical and Computer Engr.- Spring 1990 (Box Box 63)
  - Education- Spring 1990 (Box Box 63)
  - English (Cluster Core)- Spring 1990 (Box Box 63)
  - Accounting- Spring 1990 (Box Box 62)
  - American Studies- Spring 1990 (Box Box 62)
  - Art History- Spring 1990 (Box Box 62)
  - Art Studio- Spring 1990 (Box Box 62)
  - Biology- Spring 1990 (Box Box 62)
  - Chemistry- Spring 1990 (Box Box 62)
  - Communication- Spring 1990 (Box Box 62)
  - Computer Science- Spring 1990 (Box Box 1990)
  - Conflict Resolution- Spring 1990 (Box Box 62)
  - Contract Course- Spring 1990 (Box Box 62)
  - Public Affairs- Fall 1989 (Box Box 61)
  - Social Work- Fall 1989 (Box Box 61)
  - Sociology- Fall 1989 (Box Box 61)
  - University Courses- Fall 1989 (Box Box 61)
  - Math- Fall 1989 (Box Box 60)
  - Nursing- Fall 1989 (Box Box 60)
  - Operations Research and Applied Statistics- Fall 1989 (Box Box 60)
  - PAGE- Fall 1989 (Box Box 60)
  - Performing Arts (Dance, Theatre, Music)- Fall 1989 (Box Box 60)
  - Philosophy and Religion- Fall 1989 (Box Box 60)
  - Physics- Fall 1989 (Box Box 60)
  - Psychology- Fall 1989 (Box Box 60)
  - European Studies- Fall 1989 (Box Box 59)
  - Finance- Fall 1989 (Box Box 59)
  - Foreign Languages- Fall 1989 (Box Box 59)
  - Geology- Fall 1989 (Box Box 59)
  - Health, Sports and Leisure- Fall 1989 (Box Box 59)
  - History- Fall 1989 (Box Box 59)
  - Information Science and Systems Engineering- Fall 1989 (Box Box 59)
  - Latin American Studies- Fall 1989 (Box Box 59)
  - Law School- Fall 1989 (Box Box 59)
  - Management- Fall 1989 (Box Box 59)
  - Marketing- Fall 1989 (Box Box 59)
  - Economics- Fall 1989 (Box Box 58)
  - Education (Curriculum and Instruction)- Fall 1989 (Box Box 58)
  - Education (Leadership and Human Development)- Fall 1989 (Box Box 58)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Fall 1989 (Box Box 58)
  - English- Fall 1989 (Box Box 58)
  - Accounting- Fall 1989 (Box Box 57)
  - American Studies- Fall 1989 (Box Box 57)
  - Art History- Art Studio- Fall 1989 (Box Box 57)
  - Biology- Fall 1989 (Box Box 57)
  - Chemistry- Fall 1989 (Box Box 57)
  - Communication- Fall 1989 (Box Box 57)
  - Computer Science- Fall 1989 (Box Box 57)
  - Conflict Resolution- Fall 1989 (Box Box 57)
  - Contract Course- Fall 1989 (Box Box 57)
  - Decision Sciences- Fall 1989 (Box Box 57)
  - Psychology- Spring 1989 (Box Box 56)
  - Public Affairs- Spring 1989 (Box Box 56)
  - ROTC- Spring 1989 (Box Box 56)
  - Social Work- Spring 1989 (Box Box 56)
  - Sociology- Spring 1989 (Box Box 56)
  - University Courses- Spring 1989 (Box Box 56)
  - Nursing- Summer 1989 (Box Box 56)
  - Systems Engineering- Summer 1989 (Box Box 56)
  - Marketing- Spring 1989 (Box Box 55)
  - Math- Spring 1989 (Box Box 55)
  - Performing Arts (Dance, Theatre, Music)- Spring 1989 (Box Box 55)
  - Nursing- Spring 1989 (Box Box 55)
  - OP RSCH and APPL STAT- Spring 1989 (Box Box 55)
  - PAGE- Spring 1989 (Box Box 55)
  - Philosophy/Religion- Spring 1989 (Box Box 55)
  - Physics- Spring 1989 (Box Box 55)
  - European Studies- Spring 1989 (Box Box 54)
  - Finance (Box Box 54)
  - Foreign Languages- Spring 1989 (Box Box 54)
  - Geology- Spring 1989 (Box Box 54)
  - Health, Sports and Leisure Studies- Spring 1989 (Box Box 54)
  - History- Spring 1989 (Box Box 54)
  - INFO. SCI and SYS ENGR (INFS, INFT, SYST)- Spring 1989 (Box Box 54)
  - Law School- Spring 1989 (Box Box 54)
  - Management- Spring 1989 (Box Box 54)
  - Economics- Spring 1989 (Box Box 53)
  - Education- C and I- Spring 1989 (Box Box 53)
  - Education (Leadership)- Spring 1989 (Box Box 53)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Spring 1989 (Box Box 53)
  - English- Spring 1989 (Box Box 53)
  - Accounting- Spring 1989 (Box Box 52)
  - American Studies- Spring 1989 (Box Box 52)
  - Art (History, Studio)- Spring 1989 (Box Box 52)
  - Biology- Spring 1989 (Box Box 52)
  - Communications- Spring 1989 (Box Box 52)
  - Computer Science- Spring 1989 (Box Box 52)
  - Conflict Resolution- Spring 1989 (Box Box 52)
  - Contract- Spring 1989 (Box Box 52)
  - Decision Sciences (DESC, IRM) (Box Box 52)
  - Nursing- Fall 1988 (Box Box 52)
  - Operations Research and Applied Statistics- PAGE (Box Box 52)
  - Performing Arts- Philosophy / Religion- Fall 1988 (Box Box 52)
  - Physics- Psychology- Fall 1988 (Box Box 52)
  - Public Affairs- Fall 1988 (Box Box 52)
  - ROTC- University Courses- Fall 1988 (Box Box 52)
  - European Studies- Fall 1988 (Box Box 51)
  - Finance- Foreign Languages- Fall 1988 (Box Box 51)
  - Geology- Health, Sports and Leisure- Fall 1988 (Box Box 51)
  - History- Info Sci. and System Engr.- Fall 1988 (Box Box 51)
  - Management- Marketing- Fall 1988 (Box Box 51)
  - Math- Fall 1988 (Box Box 51)
  - Economics- Fall 1988 (Box Box 50)
  - Education- Fall 1988 (Box Box 50)
  - Elect. and Computer Engr.- Fall 1988 (Box Box 50)
  - English- Fall 1988 (Box Box 50)
  - English (Cluster/Core)- Fall 1988 (Box Box 50)
  - Acct./BULE- Art Studio- Fall 1988 (Box Box 49)
  - Biology- Fall 1988 (Box Box 49)
  - Chemistry- Communications- Fall 1988 (Box Box 49)
  - Computer Science- Fall 1988 (Box Box 49)
  - Conflict Resolution- Decision Sciences- Fall 1988 (Box Box 49)
  - Op. Rsch. and Appl. Stat.- Performing Arts- Spring 1988 (Box Box 48)
  - Philosophy- Physics- Spring 1988 (Box Box 48)
  - Psychology- Spring 1988 (Box Box 48)
  - Public Affairs- University Courses- Spring 1988 (Box Box 48)
  - Finance- Foreign Languages- Spring 1988 (Box Box 47)
  - Geology- History- Spring 1988 (Box Box 47)
  - Info. Sci. and Systems Engr.- Marketing- Spring 1988 (Box Box 47)
  - Math- Nursing- Spring 1988 (Box Box 47)
  - Decision Sciences- Economics- Spring 1988 (Box Box 46)
  - Education- ECE- Spring 1988 (Box Box 46)
  - English- Spring 1988 (Box Box 46)
  - Accounting- Art Studio- Spring 1988 (Box Box 45)
  - Biology- Spring 1988 (Box Box 45)
  - Chemistry- Communication- Spring 1988 (Box Box 45)
  - Computer Science- Contract Course- Spring 1988 (Box Box 45)
  - Performing Arts- Philosophy- Fall 1987 (Box Box 44)
  - Physics- Psychology- Fall 1987 (Box Box 44)
  - Public Affairs- Fall 1987 (Box Box 44)
  - ROTC- Sociology- Fall 1987 (Box Box 44)
  - University Courses- Fall 1987 (Box Box 44)
  - Geology- Health and Physical Ed.- Fall 1987 (Box Box 43)
  - History- Info. Sci. and Sys. Engr.- Fall 1987 (Box Box 43)
  - Management- Math- Fall 1987 (Box Box 43)
  - Nursing- Fall 1987 (Box Box 43)
  - Operations Research- PAGE- Fall 1987 (Box Box 43)
  - Education- Fall 1987 (Box Box 42)
  - Elect. and Computer Engineering- Fall 1987 (Box Box 42)
  - English (Cluster/Core)- Fall 1987 (Box Box 42)
  - European Studies- Foreign Languages- Fall 1987 (Box Box 42)
  - Accounting- Art Studio- Fall 1987 (Box Box 41)
  - Biology- Fall 1987 (Box Box 41)
  - Chemistry- Communication- Fall 1987 (Box Box 41)
  - Computer Science- Contract Courses- Fall 1987 (Box Box 41)
  - Decision Sciences- Economics- Fall 1987 (Box Box 41)
  - Public Affairs- Social Work- Spring 1987 (Box Box 40)
  - Sociology- University Courses- Spring 1987 (Box Box 40)
  - Nursing- PAGE- Spring 1987 (Box Box 39)
  - Performing Arts- Philosophy/Religion- Spring 1987 (Box Box 39)
  - Physics- Psychology- Spring 1987 (Box Box 39)
  - European Studies- Foreign Languages- Spring 1987 (Box Box 38)
  - Geology- Health, Sports, Leisure- Spring 1987 (Box Box 38)
  - History- Information Technology- Spring 1987 (Box Box 38)
  - Management- Military Science- Spring 1987 (Box Box 38)
  - Conflict Resolution- Economics- Spring 1987 (Box Box 37)
  - Education- Spring 1987 (Box Box 37)
  - Elect. and Computer Engineering- Spring 1987 (Box Box 37)
  - English- Spring 1987 (Box Box 37)
  - Acct./BULE- Art Studies- Spring 1987 (Box Box 36)
  - Biology- Spring 1987 (Box Box 36)
  - Chemistry- Spring 1987 (Box Box 36)
  - Communication- Computer Science- Spring 1987 (Box Box 36)
  - Health and Phys. Ed., History- Fall 1986 (Box Box 35)
  - Finance- Geology- Fall 1986 (Box Box 35)
  - Management- Military Science- Fall 1986 (Box Box 35)
  - Nursing- Fall 1986 (Box Box 35)
  - PAGE- Philosophy and Religion- Fall 1986 (Box Box 35)
  - Physics, Psychology- Fall 1986 (Box Box 35)
  - Public Affairs- Social Work- Fall 1986 (Box Box 35)
  - Sociology- Contract Courses- Fall 1986 (Box Box 35)
  - Accounting- Art Studio- Fall 1986 (Box Box 34)
  - Biology- Fall 1986 (Box Box 34)
  - Chemistry, Communication- Fall 1986 (Box Box 34)
  - Computer and Info. Science- Conflict Resolution- Fall 1986 (Box Box 34)
  - Decision Sciences, Economics- Fall 1986 (Box Box 34)
  - Education- Fall 1986 (Box Box 34)
  - Elect. and Computer Engineering- Fall 1986 (Box Box 34)
  - English- Fall 1986 (Box Box 34)
  - REUD- Contract Courses- Spring 1986 (Box Box 33)
  - Accounting- Education- Spring 1986 (Box Box 33)
  - Elect. and Computer Engineering- History- Spring 1986 (Box Box 33)
  - Management- Contract Courses- Summer 1986 (Box Box 33)
  - PAGE- Performing Arts- Fall 1985 (Box Box 32)
  - Philosophy/ Religion- Physics- Fall 1985 (Box Box 32)
  - Psychology- Fall 1985 (Box Box 32)
  - Social Work- Systems Engineering- Fall 1985 (Box Box 32)
  - Contract Courses- English Language Institute- University Courses- Fall 1985 (Box Box 32)
  - Education- Spring 1986 (Box Box 31)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Spring 1986 (Box Box 31)
  - English- Spring 1986 (Box Box 31)
  - English Language Inst.- Geology- Spring 1986 (Box Box 31)
  - Acct./BULE- Art (Studio)- Spring 1986 (Box Box 30)
  - Biology- Spring 1986 (Box Box 30)
  - Chemistry- Communication- Spring 1986 (Box Box 30)
  - Computer and Information Science- Decision Sciences- Spring 1986 (Box Box 30)
  - Economics- Spring 1986 (Box Box 30)
  - HPE- Management- Spring 1986 (Box Box 29)
  - Marketing- Nursing- Spring 1986 (Box Box 29)
  - Operations Research- Physics- Spring 1986 (Box Box 29)
  - Psychology- Public Affairs- Spring 1986 (Box Box 29)
  - European Studies- Foreign Languages- Fall 1985 (Box Box 28)
  - Geology- H and PE- Fall 1985 (Box Box 28)
  - History- Management - Fall 1985 (Box Box 28)
  - Marketing- Nursing- Fall 1985 (Box Box 28)
  - Economics- Fall 1985 (Box Box 27)
  - Education- Fall 1985 (Box Box 27)
  - Engineering- Fall 1985 (Box Box 27)
  - English- Fall 1985 (Box Box 27)
  - Accounting- Art Studio- Fall 1985 (Folder Box 26)
  - Biology- Fall 1985 (Box Box 26)
  - Chemistry- Communication- Fall 1985 (Box Box 26)
  - Computer Science- Decision Science- Fall 1985 (Box Box 26)
  - Psychology- Spring 1985 (Box Box 25)
  - Public Affairs- ROTC- Spring 1985 (Box Box 25)
  - Social Work- Spring 1985 (Box Box 25)
  - Sociology/ Anthropology/ Conflict Management- Spring 1985 (Box Box 25)
  - ELI- Systems Engineering- University Courses- Spring 1985 (Box Box 25)
  - Geology- Health and Physical Education- Spring 1985 (Box Box 24)
  - History- Management- Spring 1985 (Box Box 24)
  - Marketing- Nursing- Spring 1985 (Box Box 24)
  - Page- Performing Arts- Spring 1985 (Box Box 24)
  - Philosophy and Religion- Physics- Spring 1985 (Box Box 24)
  - Economics- Spring 1985 (Box Box 23)
  - Education- Spring 1985 (Box Box 23)
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering- Spring 1985 (Box Box 23)
  - English- Spring 1985 (Box Box 23)
  - Finance- Foreign Languages- Spring 1985 (Box Box 23)
  - Accounting/ Business Legal Studies- Spring 1985 (Box Box 22)
  - American Studies- Spring 1985 (Box Box 22)
  - Area Studies- Spring 1985 (Box Box 22)
  - Art- Spring 1985 (Box Box 22)
  - Biology- Spring 1985 (Box Box 22)
  - Chemistry- Spring 1985 (Box Box 22)
  - Communication- Spring 1985 (Box Box 22)
  - Computer and Information Science- Spring 1985 (Box Box 22)
  - Decision Sciences- Spring 1985 (Box Box 22)
  - Management- Nursing- Fall 1984 (Box Box 21)
  - PAGE- Psychology- Fall 1984 (Box Box 21)
  - Public Affairs- University Courses- Contract Courses- Fall 1984 (Box Box 21)
  - Accounting- Art Studies- Fall 1984 (Box Box 20)
  - Chemistry- Communication- Fall 1984 (Box Box 20)
  - Computer and Info. Science- Economics- Fall 1984 (Box Box 20)
  - Education- English- Fall 1984 (Box Box 20)
  - ELI- History- Fall 1984 (Box Box 20)
  - Accounting- School of Business- Spring 1984 (Box Box 19)
  - Chemistry- Decision Sciences- Spring 1984 (Box Box 19)
  - Economics- English- Spring 1984 (Box Box 19)
  - ELI- Health and PE (Box Box 19)
  - History- Nursing- Spring 1984 (Box Box 19)
  - Chemistry- Decision Sciences- Fall 1983 (Box Box 18)
  - Economics- English Language Inst.- Fall 1983 (Box Box 18)
  - Philosophy Religion- Public Affairs- Fall 1983 (Box Box 18)
  - ROTC- University Courses- Fall 1983 (Box Box 18)
  - Accounting- Control Course- Fall 1983 (Box Box 17)
  - Decision Sciences- English Language Institute- Spring 1983 (Box Box 17)
  - Economics- English Language Institute- Fall 1983 (Box Box 17)
  - Finance- Management- Fall 1983 (Box Box 17)
  - Marketing- Performing Arts- Fall 1983 (Box Box 17)
  - Philosophy and Religion- Public Affairs- Fall 1983 (Box Box 17)
  - ROTC- University Courses- Fall 1983 (Box Box 17)
  - Accounting- Chemistry- Fall 1981 (Box Box 16)
  - Communication- English- Fall 1981 (Box Box 16)
  - Finance- Mathematics- Fall 1981 (Box Box 16)
  - Nursing- Physics- Fall 1981 (Box Box 16)
  - Psychology- University Courses- Fall 1981 (Box Box 16)
  - Accounting- Communications- Spring 1982 (Box Box 16)
  - Decision Sciences- English- Spring 1982 (Box Box 16)
  - Finance- Mathematics- Spring 1982 (Box Box 16)
  - Nursing- Psychology- Spring 1982 (Box Box 16)
  - Public Affairs- University Contract, ELI, Individualized- Spring 1982 (Box Box 16)
  - Communication- Physics- Summer 1982 (Box Box 16)
  - Accounting- Foreign Languages- Fall 1982 (Box Box 16)
  - Health and PE- Social Welfare- Fall 1982 (Box Box 16)
  - Accounting- Spring 1981 (Box Box 15)
  - American Studies- Spring 1981 (Box Box 15)
  - Anthropology- Spring 1981 (Box Box 15)
  - Art- Spring 1981 (Box Box 15)
  - Astronomy- Spring 1981 (Box Box 15)
  - Biology- English- Spring 1981 (Box Box 15)
  - Finance- Theatre- Spring 1981 (Box Box 15)
  - Accounting- Decision Sciences- Fall 1980 (Box Box 14)
  - Economics- Nursing- Fall 1980 (Box Box 14)
  - Philosophy- Vietnamese- Fall 1980 (Box Box 14)
  - Accounting- Drama- Spring 1980 (Box Box 13)
  - Economics- Library Science- Spring 1980 (Box Box 13)
  - Management- Vietnamese- Spring 1980 (Box Box 13)
  - Biology- School of Business- Fall 1979 (Box Box 12)
  - Chemistry- Education- Fall 1979 (Box Box 12)
  - English- Fall 1979 (Box Box 12)
  - Fine and Performing Arts- Health and PE- Fall 1979 (Box Box 12)
  - History- Nursing- Fall 1979 (Box Box 12)
  - Philosophy/ Religion- Public Affairs- Fall 1979 (Box Box 12)
  - Sociology- University- Fall 1979 (Box Box 12)
  - Memos (Box Box 12)
  - American Studies- English- Spring 1979 (Box Box 11)
  - European Studies- Nursing- Spring 1979 (Box Box 11)
  - Philosophy- University Courses- Spring 1979 (Box Box 11)
  - American Studies- Geography- Fall 1978 (Box Box 10)
  - Geology- Speech- Fall 1978 (Box Box 10)
  - American Studies- Drama- Spring 1978 (Box Box 9)
  - Economics- Music- Spring 1978 (Box Box 9)
  - Nursing- University Courses- Spring 1978 (Box Box 9)
  - American Studies- English- Fall 1977 (Box Box 8)
  - European Studies- Music- Fall 1977 (Box Box 8)
  - Philosophy- Speech- Fall 1977 (Box Box 8)
  - American Studies- Economics- Spring 1977 (Box Box 7)
  - Education- Music- Spring 1977 (Box Box 7)
  - Philosophy- Speech- Spring 1977 (Box Box 7)
  - American Studies- Drama- Fall 1976 (Box Box 6)
  - Economics- History- Fall 1976 (Box Box 6)
  - Journalism- Physics- Fall 1976 (Box Box 6)
  - Psychology- Speech- Fall 1976 (Box Box 6)
  - American Studies- German- Spring 1976 (Box Box 5)
  - Government- Speech- Spring 1976 (Box Box 5)
  - Anthropology- Health- Fall 1975 (Box Box 4)
  - History- Speech- Fall 1975 (Box Box 4)
  - Psychology- Engineering- Fall 1974 (Box Box 3)
  - English- Speech- Fall 1974 (Box Box 3)
  - American Studies- European Studies- Fall 1974 (Box Box 2)
  - French- Physics- Fall 1974 (Box Box 2)
  - Faculty/ Course Evaluation Survey 1978 (Box Box 1)
  - Faculty/Course Evaluation Results- Spring 1975 (Box Box 1)
  - Faculty/ Course Evaluation Results 1974-75 (Box Box 1)
  - College of Professional Studies- Summer 1974, Spring 1975 (Box Box 1)
  - College of Arts and Sciences- Fall 1972 (Box Box 1)
  - Faculty/ Course Evaluation Results 1976 (Box Box 1)